Yet you still pretend not to see
Mr Fu Chenzhou
Do you take Su Mingyao
to face the future together
to respect and support her
I do
Ms Su Mengyao
Do you take Mr Fu Chenzhao
to face the future together
to respect him
and trust him
I do
Enough
Su Mengyao
every show must come to an end
Young Master Gu
This is our wedding now
Please be quiet
Fu Chenzhou
Have you forgotten your place
No I haven't
he asked me to stand here
At his wedding
It's not too much to say a word
Then let's continue the ceremony
Who allowed you to continue
Didn't you just say the wedding
no longer belongs to me
I just changed the groom
Why are you so anxious
Are you afraid I'll ruin your future
Or afraid I'll expose the truth about it
Keep Su Mingyao under control for now